A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1977-1978
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: General Records
  - Student Affairs--General--Handicapped; Easters; Events Calendar; First-Year Student Profile; Survey on Feelings, Perceptions, and Experiences; Student Activity Fee Guidelines; Graves Mountain Retreat Report; Orientation Evaluation Report (1 of 2) 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Student Affairs--General--Off-Grounds Housing (2 of 2) 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Student Council--Equal Opportunity, Student Activity Fees, Scott Stadium, Escort Service, Birdwood 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Student Council--Minutes 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Student Health--Proposed Move 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Summer Session--Reports, Summary of Courses 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - "T" Miscellaneous--Gifts; TIAA/CREF; Freedom of Speech; Marshall, Thurgood 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute--Proposal Budget 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Travel Invoices 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Treasurer 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - "U" Miscellaneous--U.N. Conference, University Family Housing 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - U.S. Savings Bonds 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Universities Research Association 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - University Guide Service 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - University Police--Alleged Harassment, Bomb Threat Procedures, Radiation Safety Response Vehicle, B & G Thefts 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - University Press of Virginia--Status Report, Survey of University Presses 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - University Relations--Visitor Information, Reorganization 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - University Union--Speakers Series 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - "V-Virginia L" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Veterans Administration, Selection of Architects, Virginia Historical Landmarks Committee re: Brooks Hall, Virginia Institute of Marine Science 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - "Virginia M-Vz" Miscellaneous--VSRS 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review--Annual Report 1977-1978 (Box 20)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation--Gifts, Tennis Courts 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - "Wa-Wh" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Affirmative Action, Undergraduate Readers' Library 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - "Wi-Wz" Miscellaneous--Gifts, Honor System, E.E. Willey, Sports Broadcasting 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous 1977-1978 (Box 22)
- Series II: Administrative Committees
  - Ad Hoc--Administrative Support Computer Facility 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Ad Hoc--Search for Dean of Division of Continuing Education 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Ad Hoc--Registrar, Search for 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Special Committee--Copeley Hill, V 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Admissions 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Afro-American Affairs Advisory 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Arboretum 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Architectural Advisory 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Athletic Advisory Council 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Calendar 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Catalogue 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Cemetery 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Chapel 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Commencement and Convocations 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittee--Processions 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittee--Public Occasions 1977-1978 (Box 22)
  - Community Colleges 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Computers 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Danforth Fellowships 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Development Steering 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Educational and Employment Opportunities, Obligations, and Rights 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Energy Conservations 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Fraternities and Sororities 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Fulbirght Grants 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Graduate Opportunities 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Graphics 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Gwathmey Award 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Housing 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - International Students 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Lectures--Page, Barbour, and James W. Richard 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Lectures--Special 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Library 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Master Plan 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Names 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Patents 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Radiation Safety 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Registration 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Rhodes Scholarship 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - ROTC 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Scheduling 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Employment Loans 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Security and General Safety 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Security and General Safety--Subcommittee--Hazardous Materials 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Student Health 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Student Activities 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Student Rights and Responsibilities 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Summer Grants 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Summer Session 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Teacher Education 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Traffic Appeals 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Traffic and Parking Committee 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - University Committee on Students 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - University Press 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - University Union 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1977-1978 (Box 23)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1977-1978 (Box 23)
- Series III: Restricted Material, 1977-1978
  - Restricted Material 1977-1978 (Box 24)